cutiegadget.com 2011-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Cutie Gadget

[Home](http://www.cutiegadget.com/) » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

> **Cutie Gadget Privacy Statement**
> 
> What written under this is the Privacy Statement for all Cutie Gadget blog including all the websites run under the www.cutiegadget.com domain.
> 
> Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.
> 
> **Email Addresses**
> 
> You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We promise that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We won’t send advertising via email. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.
> 
> **Ownership of Information**
> 
> Cutie Gadget is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.
> 
> **Commenting**
> 
> Most Cutie Gadget blog contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only.
> 
> **Cookies**
> 
>   * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
>   * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
>   * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
> 

> 
> **Traffic Reports**
> 
> Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.
> 
> **Legal proceedings**
> 
> We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but CutieGadget.com may need to disclose information when required by law.
> 
> **Business Transitions**
> 
> If CutieGadget is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.
> 
> **Links**
> 
> CutieGadget.com websites/blog frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site�s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by CutieGadget
> 
> **Notification of Changes**
> 
> When Cutie Gadget makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.
> 
> **Contact Information**
> 
> If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

Popularity: 1% [[?](http://alexking.org/projects/wordpress/popularity-contest "What does this mean?")]

Related Articles:

  1. [About](http://www.cutiegadget.com/about/ "About")
  2. [Contact The WebMaster](http://www.cutiegadget.com/contact-the-webmaster/ "Contact The WebMaster")
  3. [Disclosure Policy](http://www.cutiegadget.com/disclosure-policy/ "Disclosure Policy")
  4. [Cutie Gadget Themes](http://www.cutiegadget.com/cutie-gadget-themes/ "Cutie Gadget Themes")
